Lavina Marie Castillo Metro Phoenix Area

SUMMARY

Front-end Web Developer with a passion for the art of web development and design. I hold a certificate in Full Stack Web Development from the ASU Coding Boot Camp, a Web Development certification through Mimo, and I am currently enrolled in Google's UX Design Certification through Coursera. With a keen eye for design and a problem-solving mindset, I bring innovative solutions to create exceptional user experiences. My strengths lie in my creativity, effective teamwork, my attention to detail, and seeing projects through from initial ideation to successful execution. As I embark on this new journey into the world of development and design, I'm excited about the possibilities and I look forward to continuing to grow and contribute to my professional journey.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, CSS, HTML, Express, React, Node, Handlebars, Git, JSON, jQuery, Bootstrap, VS Code, Microsoft Office, Figma, Canva, IBM Maximo, Adobe, SQL, MongoDB, Insomnia

PROJECTS

Hire Me, Find Your Perfect Candidate (current/final project for ASU)

Active Heroku URL: https://obscure-dusk-41418-6f9c2367f998.herokuapp.com

- Summary: Active Candidate Web App for Employers
- Role: Design, Styling & Logo
- Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node, Git

My React Portfolio

Active GitHub URL: https://wht-rbt.github.io/My-React-Portfolio/

- Summary: Current Portfolio
- Role: Sole Author
- Tools: JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, Node, JSON, Git

My Bucket List

GitHub repo: https://github.com/WHT-RBT/React-BucketList.git

- Summary: Weather app that provides current and future weather forecasts
- Role: Sole Author
- Tools: JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, JSON, Git

Dish Hunt

GitHub repo: https://github.com/WHT-RBT/Dish-Hunt.git

- Summary: Food & Recipe Sharing Web App
- Role: Frontend, Design, Styling & Logo
- Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Handlebars, Node, Git

Lavina Marie Castillo Metro Phoenix Area

EDUCATION

- ASU Bootcamp | Full Stack Web Development | April 2023 October 2023
- Google | UX Design | September 2023 Present
- Mimo | Web Development | July 2023
- Fields EAM | IBM Maximo Modules | October 2015 Dec 2015
- Oxnard College | Professional Office Skills | Nov 1998 Feb 1999

Please visit my LinkedIn profile to view a list of my certifications: www.linkedin.com/in/lavinacastillo

EXPERIENCE

BSR/Account Manager, Timberlake Cabinetry

Jan 2022 - Present Mesa, AZ

Order processing and data entry of builder direct customer orders, processing all cabinet and parts orders released by the builder. Scheduling field services and installations. Manage customer information related to starts, schedules, selections, process purchase orders and warranty requests from the Builders internet-based systems. Perform pre-calls for delivery and installation, as needed, to confirm builder's delivery and installation. Develop and maintain a proficient working knowledge of Maestro, Order Billing System (OBS), Quality Management Systems (QMS), and other American Woodmark Corporation (AWC) proprietary systems. Develop an extensive knowledge product base. Schedule and assign installations. Verify ship and installation dates per builders' release and schedule. Research and schedule service/ warranty requests. Coordinate, if necessary, deliveries for installations and service items.

Business Services, Eurest Services for Johnson & Johnson Co. Nov 2018 - Jan 2020 Irving, TX

Manage manufacturing site's hard and soft services, including Janitorial, Landscaping, Security, Pest Control, and Handyman services. Responsible for creating, distributing, and managing work orders within the customer cmms system (Maximo). Data entry of all assets, job plans, PMs, and complete and close work orders in Maximo on behalf of technicians. Monthly and quarterly reporting for all Facilities work orders, and site inspections and track all data. Vendor management and invoice approval.

Maximo Support/Planner, Eurest Services for Johnson & Johnson Apr 2015 - Oct 2018 Santa Barbara, CA Maximo Admin support for supported Johnson & Johnson sites in California, including creation, data entry and updates of all assets, job plans, PMs, service requests and work orders with planning and scheduling for several sites. Complete and close Work Orders on behalf of technicians. Create monthly, custom and quarterly reports. Travel to supported sites to train new technicians and employees in Maximo and data entry of all assets, job plans and PMs for new sites within Maximo (cmms).

Lavina Marie Castillo Metro Phoenix Area

Apr 2015-Sep 2017

Manage decommissioning team and decommissioning project for Johnsons & Johnson's Mentor site in Santa Barbara, including planning of site's last day of employment. Manage vendors for all data center, laboratory, warehouse, office space decommissioning, solar panel removal and relocation, E-waste removal, building cleanup and final inspections with landlord and owners. Create, schedule, plan and maintain building's maintenance and repair, continue site payments for rent, utilities and all facility invoices until end of lease (September 2017).

Facilities Coordinator, Mentor WW, a Johnson & Johnson Co. May 2007 - Apr 2015 Santa Barbara, CA

Maintain Facilities Helpdesk ticketing system, receiving and assigning work orders, and tracking service requests to ensure they are fulfilled in a timely manner. Maintain access badge database with building security team to activate and terminate building access as needed. Manage blanket purchase orders and correspond with vendors regarding invoices and payments. Receive, manage and pay site's rent and utilities. Provide ergonomic evaluations and purchase supplies for employees. Manage Fire Extinguisher and Eyewash station inspections, including Forklift and Picker inspections. Manage all vendors (Canteen café, fitness center, janitorial, fire system, and all building maintenance including heating and air, telephone, security, plumbing, lighting and ground maintenance). Manage all administrative, technical, and clerical operations for the department, including processing all POs, and scheduling Technicians Safety Training and First Responder's CPR and Defibrillator training. Assist in the scheduling and planning of department moves, including managing movers, and assisting IT with computer and equipment relocation. Provide support for all company social events (holiday parties, company picnics, and special events). Schedule and coordinate conference and town hall center. Backup support for Front Desk Security, IT Helpdesk and Shipping & Receiving. Order and maintain corporate office, building and warehouse supplies.

Office Manager/Billing Clerk, David C. Gore, CFA

Jun 2004 - Jan 2011 Santa Barbara, CA

Provide administrative support, including office correspondence, client invoicing, data collecting from several financial reports, order all office supplies, equipment and furniture. File management and creation of all new financial accounts for clients, reconciliations of all client statements, and management of all office maintenance and janitorial.

Executive Assistant, Somera Capital Management, LLC Nov 1999 - A

Nov 1999 - Apr 2004 Santa Barbara, CA

Provide Administrative support for VP-Acquisitions and VP-General Counsel. Responsible for research, approval and ordering of all office orders, office equipment and office furniture. Receive, code, and approve all expense statements, office invoices, utilities, and rent. Schedule and coordinate all office meetings. Create and maintain the office filing system for property investments and investor filing. Receive and track all incoming investment checks. Travel arrangements for VP-Acquisitions and VP-General Counsel. Manage, program and maintain office telephone system and office equipment. Assist in creating and distributing property acquisitions, and monthly reports. Assist CFO in organizing, sorting, assembly, quality control and processing of investor quarterly distributions